You may have noticed I don't really talk about US politics that much anymore because US politics is
I'm not saying that your local politics is not important. It very much is.
What I am saying is that for many folks, it stops there or it stops at the electoral level
or it stops at the excitement of some individual in their corner being elected. And I want you to
know that it is much bigger than that. As many folks continue to stay embroiled in the futile
conversation around elections in the United States as if they are fair, I want us to open
our aperture to see what's going on globally so that we can truly understand what we're
facing here and what we're going to need to do. Since World War II, the families that control
the central banking system, which is based in Switzerland, but as we know, operates all over
the world, have used the United States and Israel to interfere in elections all over the world
in order to amass an incredible amount of wealth and power while also suppressing that of the
people and stealing their resources. They do this oftentimes through putting leaders in power
that they control. A part of that PSYOP is convincing us here in the United States that they're not doing
that here in the United States, even though we do not have resources that we control. They are
absolutely putting who they want in power. Going back to when they did so in and on and to in the
current present day, Colombia's elections were tampered with. Peru's current elections were
tampered with. In both of these cases, the person put in place is somebody who is a part of the fascist
world order. Leftist leaders are being defeated all over the world because of United States and
central banking interference in their elections. So as excited as many of you all are about so-called
progress being made by DSA candidates in New York winning their primaries and calling them leftists
and socialists, which they are not, they give you scraps to keep you distracted, satiated, and happy
while building the walls around you.
It's the United States PSYOP that has many of us only considering ourselves and not realizing that
there's an entire globe around us and that it is coming back to us. I want you to open your aperture
because your small little world of New York is going to be crushed by the global fascism that
is rising. So I beg of you to stop putting air into the conversation and instead open your aperture.
The world is growing fascist all around you. How are you going to stay standing when it happens
and stand up to put it down? Those are the only conversations we need to be having.
They is them and who they be.